Tessl is the package manager for skills and context. Skills are a powerful tool for steering
agent behavior, expanding on things like editing your agents.md or adding documentation. But
managing skills requires more than just copying words around. You need to think about how do you
own them over time? Are they effective? And which skills do you choose in the first place? If you
are consuming skills, Tessl helps you install any skill and keeps a record in a tessl.json
file that remembers which skills are installed and helps you update them and manage them over
time. It includes evaluation for every skill that you consume, which lets you choose which one is
correct and which one is not. And it seamlessly installs them for all the agents you have without
duplicating content inside your repository. If you are producing skills of your own,
Tessl helps you evaluate and optimize them, making sure your skills are as good as they
can be. It then helps you publish and version them so users can know what they are using and
make sure they're always on the latest and greatest. Finally, it helps you keep skills
fresh by tracking related software changes and updating your skill if needed. This ensures that
your skill doesn't go stale and misguide agents. Skills and context are more than just words. They
are the unit of software in the world of agentic development. Tessl is a developer
grade package manager for skills and context and the development platform for managing context in
your organization. Making sure your agents get the right context at the right time. Get started
for free at tessl.io/registry or contact us if you want to try within your organization.